<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tornike Razmadze</title>
    <link>https://tornike.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tornike Razmadze</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tornike.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning (Coursera)</title>
      <link>https://tornike.me/posts/machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tornike.me/posts/machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve started (again) a course of Machine Learning on Coursera. These are some notes about the course.
Machine Learning problems can be seperated into two major parts: Supervised and Unsupervised machine learning.
Supervised machine learning is when we have some right answers for some amount of inputs and want to predict right anwsers for different inputs.
In Unsupervised machine learning programs we does not have any right anwsers it makes clastering of data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://tornike.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tornike.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Software Engineer, Developer, Go enthusiast (Gopher).
More Then 15 Years of Working Experience  My first computer was IBM XT 286. I was seven when we got one. After that moment I wanted to know everything about computers. My father did some coding back then and I was sitting next to him watching all those strange combinations of &amp;ldquo;words&amp;rdquo; and symbols and I knew that I wanted to learn it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://tornike.me/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tornike.me/projects/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash;&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;!&amp;ndash;
   -- MyDoc MyDoc is a SaaS platform, It&amp;rsquo;s a tool for building telemedical platform on top of the existing flow, that would enable healthcare providers to simplify and accelerate all types of communication, to reduce costs of provided services and much more.
Features:
 Symptom Checker, Health History Management, AI Based Diagnosis, Medical Document Sharing, Text/Video/Audio Chat
 Built using:
 Go, Node.js, VueJS, Vuex, Nuxt, Postgres, Docker, Micro-services</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>