<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tornike Razmadze</title><link>https://tornike.me/</link><description>Recent content on Tornike Razmadze</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tornike.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Machine Learning (Coursera)</title><link>https://tornike.me/posts/machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tornike.me/posts/machine-learning/</guid><description>Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve started (again) a course of Machine Learning on Coursera. These are some notes about the course.
Machine Learning problems can be seperated into two major parts: Supervised and Unsupervised machine learning.
Supervised machine learning is when we have some right answers for some amount of inputs and want to predict right anwsers for different inputs.
In Unsupervised machine learning programs we does not have any right anwsers it makes clastering of data.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://tornike.me/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tornike.me/projects/</guid><description>MyDoc MyDoc is a SaaS platform, It&amp;rsquo;s a tool for building telemedical platform on top of the existing flow, that would enable healthcare providers to simplify and accelerate all types of communication, to reduce costs of provided services and much more.
Features:
Symptom Checker, Health History Management, AI Based Diagnosis, Medical Document Sharing, Text/Video/Audio Chat
Built using:
Go, Node.js, VueJS, Vuex, Nuxt, Postgres, Docker, Micro-services
Content Management System Custom Content Management System (CMS) for governmental, nongovernmental and media agencies.</description></item><item><title>Tornike Razmadze</title><link>https://tornike.me/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tornike.me/about/</guid><description>Software Architect, Engineer, Developer.
Work Experience SkyGroup Principal Architect / Lead Engineer (Dec 2018 - Present)
Write code 3-4 hours a day. Mostly work on project architecture, after the project is on the right track gradually move to just reviewing code. Manage team of 20 members mostly software engineers, including frontend, backend and data engineers. MyDoc Senior Software Engineer / Software Architect / Co-Founder (Jun 2017 - Present)
Created the prototype of the product.</description></item></channel></rss>